We are excited to announce a
breakthrough in memory for agents.
Introducing Cogni, the world's most
accurate open-source memory platform.
Cogni can handle 100 billion token
context windows, far beyond the limits
of models like Claude Opus 4.8 and GPT
5.5. At this window, Cogni hits more
than 79% [music]
accuracy while costing seven times less
than top models, an unprecedented feat
for LLM memory. Let me show you how
powerful Cogni is. Let's say you are a
developer and want to secure a $1
million deal. Here we have [music] a
regular session of Claude code in our
terminal, and here is a session of
Claude code using Cogni. We'll ask both
the same prompt, "Build an app for this
prospect, make me a millionaire, and
make [music] no mistakes." First, our
standard Claude session finds a
transcript from three weeks ago when the
prospect discusses Windows architecture.
But there is an issue. Last week, the
prospect told you they switched from
Windows to macOS. Claude was overloaded
with context as it retrieved five
different meeting transcripts with this
prospect. So it didn't connect the dots,
and it simply slipped through the
cracks. Next, Claude delivered a Windows
file incompatible with prospect's macOS
system, [music] immediately killing the
deal. Now we'll take a look at Cogni's
session, connected to our company's data
through Agents, Notion, and Slack. Just
like human brains do, Cogni not only
retrieves the context, but it
understands the relationships between
the data, so it always knows what's most
relevant right now and why. It knows
this $1 million prospect has [music] now
changed to macOS. It knows their most
up-to-date vision for the app even after
three different shifts to their
perspective, [music]
and even recognizes the prospect is
similar to a client you closed six
months ago having the same stack and
buying triggers. So it pulls the
client's winning app playbook and builds
directly into this one. Now, Cogni runs
into an issue. It finds a few different
pieces of conflicting information about
what flows should be used for the app.
Claude without Cogni would get stuck in
a loop for 20 minutes, burn millions of
tokens, and still hallucinate. But Cogni
doesn't guess, and it also doesn't ask
you for input. Cogni retraces the chain
of decisions, identifies which meetings
came later, verifies who made the final
call, corrects its own memory, and moves
forward with the correct version on its
own.
Claude and ChatGPT use basic vector
memory, a flat pile of facts with no
relationships between them, treated the
same way for every conversation.
But, Cogni uses frontier dynamic [music]
graph memory, which connects
relationships between everything it
knows, updates the context every day,
and always knows what matters right now.
Cogni is built by neuroscience
researchers from universities of Brown
and Berkeley. [music]
Over a hundred of the world's
fastest-growing companies, like Bayer,
use Cogni already. To celebrate our
launch, we're giving away the exact
playbook we used to boost Cogni's cloud
code output by 400% through accurate,
persistent, and contextually relevant
memory. The right operator could use the
framework to make an extra seven or
eight figures a year. Leave a comment,
and we'll send [music] it to you.